http://www.lankar.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Privacy Policyadmin2018-11-19T08:02:04+00:00
Privacy Policy
Please read our Privacy Policy carefully so that you can understand how we collect, use and disclose the personal
information that you provide to us.
By accessing this Website you accept all the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. In particular, by submitting
your personal data to us, you will be deemed to have given your permission for use and disclosures referred to herein.
If you do not agree with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, you must immediately cease using and accessing
this Website and any content, services or products contained in or available from this Website for which you need to
provide personal information.
What does this privacy policy cover?
This Privacy Policy covers our use and disclosure of your personal information, which is collected through or in connection with this
Website and all other Software created by Autogence Inc. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, “this Website” means all the web pages
and all other software related to Autogence Inc. excluding any links to third party sites.
Who is responsible for the personal information collected on this Website?
Autogence Inc. whose registered office is at Ontario Canada controls the personal data collected on this Website.
Special Notice – if you are under 18 years old
Autogence Inc. does not intentionally collect personal data of persons under 18 years old. If you are under 18 years old
please do not send us your personal information (for example, your name, address and email address). If you are under
18 years old and you wish to ask a question or use this Website in anyway which requires you to submit your personal
information please get your parent or guardian to do so on your behalf.
Information collection and use
We collect and use personal information (including but not limited to; name, address, telephone number and email address)
in order to:
respond to queries or requests submitted by you
process orders or applications submitted by you
administer or otherwise carry out our obligations in relation to any agreement you have with us
anticipate and resolve problems with any products or services supplied to you
better tailor and improve the features of products and services
create products or services that may meet your needs.
As part of the products or services offered to you through our Website, the information you provide to us may be
transferred to countries outside of Canada.
By way of example, this may happen if any of our servers are from time to time located in a country outside of Canada
or one of our service providers is located in a country outside of Canada.
These countries may not have similar data protection laws to Canada.
If we transfer your information outside of Canada in this way, we will take steps to ensure that your privacy rights
continue to be protected.
In addition, if you use our services while you are outside Canada, your information may be transferred outside Canada in
order to provide you with those services.
We may use third parties for the fulfilment of our obligations hereunder.
However, except as set out in this Privacy Policy, we will not disclose any personally identifiable information without your
permission unless we are legally entitled or required to do so (for example, if required to do so by legal process or for
the purposes of prevention of fraud or other crime) or if we believe that such action is necessary to protect and/or defend
our rights, property or personal safety and those of our users/customers etc.
In the event our company, or part thereof, is acquired by another company, that company may use your personal data in
accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Providing you with additional information and sharing your information
From time to time we would like to use your personal information for purposes other than as set out in the above section.
We believe that these additional uses will be of benefit to you. However, we understand that you may not wish us to use
your information in this way.
We will not use your information for the purposes set out below if you have indicated that you do not wish us to use your
information in this way when submitting the information.
Additionally, if at any time you wish us to stop using your information for any or all of the below purposes, please let us
know (see contact information below).
We will take the necessary steps to stop the use of your information for such purposes with immediate effect.
In such case we will, however, continue to use your personal data for the purposes set out in the above section for as
long as necessary to achieve such purposes.
From time to time we will use the information you supply to us for:
market research and tracking of sales data
informing you about our products and services, which may include contacting you by telephone
giving the information to Autogence offices and companies, which may be located outside Canada, to enable them to send
you information which may be of interest to you.
In addition, from time to time we would like to give your name, address and e-mail and any other personal data you supply to
us to carefully selected third parties, which may be located outside of Canada. These third parties may use this information for:
market research and tracking of sales data
sending you information about their products and services
giving the information to their affiliate offices and companies to enable them to send you information which may be of interest to you.
Collection of non-personal information
We may automatically collect non-personal information about you such as the type of internet browsers you use or
the website from which you linked to our Website. We may also aggregate details which you have submitted to the
Website (for example, your age and the town where you live). You cannot be identified from this information and it
is only used to assist us in providing an effective service on this web site.
We may from time to time supply third parties with this non-personal or aggregated data for uses in connection with this Website.
The use of cookies
We may store some information (commonly known as a “cookie”) on your computer when you look at our Website. We are able to read
these cookies for information purposes when you revisit our Website.
The type of information we collect as a result of a cookie being accepted by you is specific to your PC and includes the IP address, the
date and time the PC visited the Website, what parts of our Website were looked at and whether the web pages requested were
delivered successfully. This information is anonymous; it represents a computer rather than a person.
We use the cookie information to improve our knowledge of the use of our Website and to enable us to be able to ascertain whether the
Website is operating at an optimal level. This allows us to enhance our web offerings to you and to provide an enjoyable and an
innovative online experience.
You can erase or block this information by changing the settings on your computer (please refer to your help screens or manuals).
If you do erase or block this information you may not be able to utilise some or all of the features of the Website.
Chat rooms, notice boards, newsgroups
If at any time this Website offers any chat rooms, notice board facilities, newsgroups etc we may collect the information that you disclose.
Such information will be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Please note that we cannot be responsible for other parties’ use of
the personal information, which you make available to such third parties through any chat room, notice board, newsgroup etc on this Website.
Please be careful about what personal information you disclose in this way.
E-mail, Feedback and Forum Facilities
If at any time this Website offers any e-mail, feedback or forum facilities, we may collect the information, which you disclose. Such information
will be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Keeping our records accurate
We aim to keep our information about you as accurate as possible. If you would like to review or change the details you have supplied us
with, please contact us as set out below.
Security of your personal data
We have implemented technology and policies with the objective of protecting your privacy from unauthorised access and improper use and
will update these measures as new technology becomes available, as appropriate.
Use of your personal information submitted to other websites
We cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other websites even if:
you accessed the third party website using links from our Website; or
you linked to our Website from a third party website.
We recommend that you check the policy of each site you visit and contact the owner or operator of such website if you have any concerns or questions.
Submission of others personal information
From time to time this Website may ask you to provide personal details of your family or friends, for example, so that we can send them details of our
products and services. Before providing such information, please ensure that you have obtained their consent to their personal data being used in this
way. We will not use these details in any manner, which is incompatible with this Privacy Policy.
Will this privacy policy change?
From time to time we may make changes to this Privacy Policy.
Please check our Privacy Policy on a regular basis.
How you can contact us
If you would like to contact Autogence about our Privacy Policy, you can do so by e-mailing eteam@lankar.com
